siam.org 2008-06-23

# SIAM: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

### **Effective Date: September, 2006**

### **Our Policy**

The Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics ("SIAM," "we" or "us") respects and understands its customers’ concerns about confidentiality and privacy, and we take appropriate and reasonable steps to ensure that any information you give us is handled in a safe and responsible manner.  Because of our respect and understanding, we have developed this Privacy Policy which discloses the privacy practices of SIAM and describes the information we collect about you during your use of the Web site and what use we may make of that information. 

It is important to remember that by using our Web site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  We suggest that you refer to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis as it may change, at any time in SIAM's sole discretion, in order to allow us to take advantage of technological advances or for business purposes or legal reasons.

### **Information Collection and Usage**

To facilitate a more intuitive and easy to use our Web site, we may automatically track certain information about you. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address.  Many sites automatically collect this information.  We do not collect or use this information to create a profile about you.  We may also decide to use cookies on certain pages of our site.  Cookies can help us provide information which is targeted to your interests.  Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site.  Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. 

We may also use personally identifiable information to deliver information that, in some cases, is targeted to your needs and interests, such as promotional e-mails, targeted banners and promotions.  If you supply us with your e-mail or mailing address, you may receive occasional mail from us announcing services, product information, promotional events or other official communications in regard to our society. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please send us an e-mail to service@SIAM.org indicating your e-mail address or mailing address as applicable and asking us to remove you from our mailing list. 

Unfortunately, we cannot ensure that information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.  There is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet regardless of our efforts. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), third parties may unlawfully intercept or access files, transmissions or private communications.  Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect information, we can not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. **                                                                                                                                                      **

**Third Party Collectors of Information** **Service Providers:** We provide information to third parties to help us bring you the products or services we offer.  

**Third Party Offers:** On occasion, we may provide your name and postal mailing address to responsible outside companies that we carefully evaluate so they can let you know about their products or services that we think might be of interest to you.  If you prefer that we NOT share your name and mailing address with any outside companies for the purposes of Third Party Offers, you may opt out by:

        * writing to us at SIAM at the address given below 
        * calling us at  (worldwide) +1-215-382-9800, Toll free (USA and Canada) 1-800-447-SIAM
        * Faxing us at +1-215-386-7999
        * E-mailing us at [service@siam.org](mailto:service@SIAM.org)  

We will make every effort to implement your choice as soon as possible.

### **Legal Disclosures**

We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you as required by law, including voluntary disclosures to law enforcement agencies and government officials, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Our Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information SIAM collects from you. The SIAM Web site may contain links to other sites, however, and SIAM is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those external sites.

###   
**Security**

We use industry standard Secure Socket Layer software (SSL) to encrypt your personal and credit card information during the order checkout process.  When you make a purchase via our Web site, we obtain from you information that we need to complete your transaction.  From your transactions, we obtain information concerning the specific products you purchase. 

### **Notification of Material Changes to this Policy**

This Section identifies material changes to this Policy since the Effective Date.  
[None at present.]

### **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review, change or remove your personal information, you can:

  * e-mail us at [service@siam.org](mailto:service@siam.org)
  * Phone us at (worldwide) +1-215-382-9800, Toll free (USA and Canada) 1-800-447-SIAM 
  * Fax us at +1-215-386-7999 
  * You can contact us by writing to: 

Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics  
3600 Market Street, 6th Floor  
Philadelphia, PA 19104-2688.
